<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on ギークブログ</title>
    <link>http://localhost/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on ギークブログ</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 20:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started</title>
      <link>http://localhost/posts/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost/posts/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Geekblog is a simple Hugo theme for personal blogs. It is intentionally designed as a fast and lean theme and may not fit the requirements of complex websites. If a more feature-complete theme is required there are a lot of got alternatives out there. This post helps you to get started with the Geekblog theme, including initial setup and basic configuration.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simple sticky posts</title>
      <link>http://localhost/posts/sticky/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jun 2020 00:06:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost/posts/sticky/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sticky (or pinned) posts implementation is currently really simple and handled by &lt;code&gt;weight: 1&lt;/code&gt; in a post front matter.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;$$ e^{\pi i} = \sqrt{2} $$&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown syntax</title>
      <link>http://localhost/posts/markdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost/posts/markdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emoji Support</title>
      <link>http://localhost/posts/emojies/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2020 19:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost/posts/emojies/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emoji can be enabled in a Hugo project in a number of ways.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Post with images</title>
      <link>http://localhost/posts/post-with-images/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost/posts/post-with-images/</guid>
      <description>Amalia id per in minimum facility, quid facet modifier ea ma. Ill um select ma ad, en ferric patine sentient vim. Per expendable foreordained interpretations cu, maxim sole pertinacity in ram. Dolor sit, sumo unique argument um no. Gracie nominal id xiv. Romanesque acclimates investiture. Ornateness bland it ex enc, est yeti am bongo detract re. Pro ad prompts feud gait, quid exercise emeritus bis e. In pro quints consequent, denim fastidious copious quo ad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short post</title>
      <link>http://localhost/posts/post-short/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 20:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost/posts/post-short/</guid>
      <description>Dolor sit, sumo unique argument um no. Gracie nominal id xiv. Romanesque acclimates investiture. Ornateness bland it ex enc, est yeti am bongo detract re. Pro ad prompts feud gait, quid exercise emeritus bis e. In pro quints consequent, denim fastidious copious quo ad. Stet probates in duo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
